<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on OrganGrinderrr</title>
    <link>https://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on OrganGrinderrr</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Money Heist</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/a-sample-story3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/a-sample-story3/</guid>
      <description>What is perfect money heist, an operation that is stealth. no one even notice that they&amp;rsquo;ve been robbed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Personality That Would Fight Back</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/a-sample-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/a-sample-story/</guid>
      <description>Chapter 1: The Havoc family # Hugo was born and raised in a poor village. He has a psychotic family line, spanning across multiple generations. His whole childhood was full of crap. His parents would get into a fight every other day. Always felt like this family was a wrecking ship, at risk of sinking with each wave crashing fight. Despite his best efforts of screaming and yelling for help, nobody ever answered back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Sample Archlinux Dotfiles for Hackers</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/a-sample-dotfiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/a-sample-dotfiles/</guid>
      <description>A little bit opinion on Linux distros # Ubuntu, Archlinux, Gentoo, NixOS, Qubes OS, Tails Personally I would kill Qubes and Tails already, rather than chosing a distro designed for a single purpose, I would rather chose a general purpose. As everything in qubes can be implemented in other general purpose systems. Qubes and Tails are not alien technologies.&#xA;Using Qubes and tails in my humble opinion not doing you any good as it shouts out that you are special, or more than special.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain Tumor</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/a-sample-story2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/a-sample-story2/</guid>
      <description>My name is Shawn. Nearly 4 months ago, I became very slient, usually I talk more, not as laqucious but people notces my existence. This change of personality is all because of a brain Tumor.&#xA;Doctor says half a year, tops, I will be gone. Hard to accept the truth, even now. worked all my life to get to this point, that is really tragic, my son just got a new born baby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Rambling I</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/some-rambling-1728944813/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/some-rambling-1728944813/</guid>
      <description>When someone write on their profile saying, they are a chaos lover, they listen to minor music. their tastes are really special. and that&amp;rsquo;s what makes them special. I dispite them. Not bcuz I&amp;rsquo;m really the one who is special. but bcuz Sometimes they just stuck in their poor logic.&#xA;when you heard people say, why they always judge without knowing. I ask them, do you know what&amp;rsquo;s even worse? judge with knowing, or real judgement, that include judge in action, not only just saying it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Guide to Privacy</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/ultimate-guide-to-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/ultimate-guide-to-privacy/</guid>
      <description> # </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
